{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the main protagonist of the Naruto series?",
      "answers": ["Sasuke", "Naruto", "Kakashi", "Sakura"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Naruto's father?",
      "answers": ["Jiraiya", "Minato", "Orochimaru", "Hiruzen"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Naruto's mother?",
      "answers": ["Kushina", "Mikoto", "Tsunade", "Inoichi"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Nine-Tailed Fox that attacked Konoha?",
      "answers": ["Kurama", "Isobu", "Matatabi", "Gyuki"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Naruto's signature technique?",
      "answers": [
        "Rasengan",
        "Chidori",
        "Fireball Jutsu",
        "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Hidden Village where Naruto lives?",
      "answers": ["Sunagakure", "Konohagakure", "Kirigakure", "Iwagakure"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first Hokage of Konoha?",
      "answers": [
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Hashirama Senju",
        "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
        "Danzo Shimura"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second Hokage of Konoha?",
      "answers": [
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Hashirama Senju",
        "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
        "Danzo Shimura"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the third Hokage of Konoha?",
      "answers": [
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Hashirama Senju",
        "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
        "Danzo Shimura"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the current Hokage of Konoha?",
      "answers": [
        "Kakashi Hatake",
        "Tsunade Senju",
        "Naruto Uzumaki",
        "Shikamaru Nara"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the strongest member of the Akatsuki?",
      "answers": ["Itachi Uchiha", "Pain", "Kisame Hoshigaki", "Sasori"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the Akatsuki?",
      "answers": ["Itachi Uchiha", "Pain", "Kisame Hoshigaki", "Madara Uchiha"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the youngest member of the Rookie Nine?",
      "answers": [
        "Naruto Uzumaki",
        "Sakura Haruno",
        "Sasuke Uchiha",
        "Hinata Hyuga"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the teacher of the Rookie Nine?",
      "answers": [
        "Orochimaru",
        "Kakashi Hatake",
        "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
        "Jiraiya"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the organization that Orochimaru founded?",
      "answers": ["Root", "Akatsuki", "Sound Four", "Sannin"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the strongest member of the Sannin?",
      "answers": ["Orochimaru", "Jiraiya", "Tsunade Senju", "Kabuto Yakushi"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the legendary ninja known as the \"Copy Ninja\"?",
      "answers": ["Itachi Uchiha", "Pain", "Kakashi Hatake", "Madara Uchiha"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Naruto's rival?",
      "answers": ["Sasuke Uchiha", "Gaara", "Neji Hyuga", "Shikamaru Nara"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the Sound Four?",
      "answers": ["Orochimaru", "Kabuto Yakushi", "Kimim", "Sakon and Ukon"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the group that Gaara leads?",
      "answers": ["Akatsuki", "Sound Four", "Suna Council", "Sand Siblings"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the strongest member of the Sound Four?",
      "answers": ["Kimimaro", "Jirobo", "Kidomaru", "Tayuya"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the curse mark that Orochimaru uses?",
      "answers": [
        "Sharingan",
        "Mangekyo Sharingan",
        "Cursed Seal of Heaven",
        "Cursed Seal of Earth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the former member of the Akatsuki who becomes the leader of the Hidden Rain Village?",
      "answers": ["Nagato Uzumaki", "Yahiko", "Konan", "Hanzo"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first member of the Rookie Nine to become a Chunin?",
      "answers": [
        "Naruto Uzumaki",
        "Sakura Haruno",
        "Sasuke Uchiha",
        "Shikamaru Nara"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja clan that Sasuke belongs to?",
      "answers": ["Uchiha", "Hyuga", "Nara", "Aburame"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the Uchiha clan?",
      "answers": [
        "Sasuke Uchiha",
        "Fugaku Uchiha",
        "Itachi Uchiha",
        "Mikoto Uchiha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Uchiha clan's kekkei genkai?",
      "answers": ["Sharingan", "Byakugan", "Rinnegan", "Mangekyo Sharingan"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Uchiha clan who massacres the entire clan?",
      "answers": [
        "Sasuke Uchiha",
        "Itachi Uchiha",
        "Fugaku Uchiha",
        "Mikoto Uchiha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the organization that Itachi works for?",
      "answers": ["Akatsuki", "Anbu", "Root", "Leaf Police"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Uchiha clan who helps Naruto during the Fourth Great Ninja War?",
      "answers": [
        "Itachi Uchiha",
        "Shisui Uchiha",
        "Obito Uchiha",
        "Madara Uchiha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the jinchuriki of the Two-Tailed Monster Cat?",
      "answers": ["Yugito Nii", "Gaara", "Killer Bee", "Han"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the group that Killer Bee belongs to?",
      "answers": [
        "Akatsuki",
        "Seven Swordsmen of the Mist",
        "Kumogakure",
        "Jinchuriki Alliance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the Seven Swordsmen of the Mist?",
      "answers": [
        "Zabuza Momochi",
        "Kisame Hoshigaki",
        "Mangetsu Hozuki",
        "Chojuro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Seven Swordsmen of the Mist who wields the Samehada sword?",
      "answers": [
        "Zabuza Momochi",
        "Kisame Hoshigaki",
        "Mangetsu Hozuki",
        "Chojuro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the group that Madara Uchiha leads?",
      "answers": [
        "Akatsuki",
        "Uchiha Clan",
        "Tobi and the White Zetsu Army",
        "Uchiha Restoration Army"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the jinchuriki of the One-Tailed Shukaku?",
      "answers": ["Naruto Uzumaki", "Gaara", "Killer Bee", "Yugito Nii"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of the White Zetsu Army?",
      "answers": [
        "Madara Uchiha",
        "Obito Uchiha",
        "Kaguya Otsutsuki",
        "Black Zetsu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja who creates the Edo Tensei jutsu?",
      "answers": [
        "Orochimaru",
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
        "Danzo Shimura"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first Hokage's younger brother?",
      "answers": [
        "Hashirama Senju",
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Kawarama Senju",
        "Itama Senju"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second Hokage's younger brother?",
      "answers": [
        "Hashirama Senju",
        "Tobirama Senju",
        "Kawarama Senju",
        "Itama Senju"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Akatsuki who uses puppets as his primary fighting style?",
      "answers": ["Sasori", "Deidara", "Hidan", "Kakuzu"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first jinchuriki of the Eight-Tailed Ox?",
      "answers": ["Killer Bee", "Yugito Nii", "Han", "FÅ«"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja who becomes Tsunade's assistant?",
      "answers": ["Shizune", "Ayame", "Mei Terumi", "Kurenai Yuhi"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja who is known as the \"Goddess of Healing\"?",
      "answers": [
        "Tsunade Senju",
        "Sakura Haruno",
        "Ino Yamanaka",
        "Rin Nohara"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Akatsuki who has the ability to absorb chakra?",
      "answers": ["Nagato Uzumaki", "Konan", "Hidan", "Kakuzu"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first Hokage's granddaughter?",
      "answers": [
        "Tsunade Senju",
        "Mei Terumi",
        "Kurenai Yuhi",
        "Mito Uzumaki"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the organization that Danzo Shimura leads?",
      "answers": ["Anbu", "Root", "Akatsuki", "Leaf Police"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja who becomes the Fifth Kazekage?",
      "answers": ["Gaara", "Temari", "Kankuro", "Baki"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the member of the Akatsuki who has the ability to control paper?",
      "answers": ["Konan", "Pain", "Itachi Uchiha", "Kisame Hoshigaki"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the ninja who becomes the Fifth Mizukage?",
      "answers": ["Mei Terumi", "Chojuro", "Ao", "Yagura"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
